// Kists all questions and answers to each question
let level1Questions = [
	{
		question: "Which club has won the most English Premier League titles?",
		answer: "Manchester United",
		options: ["Arsenal", "Liverpool", "Manchester United", "Chelsea"],
	},
	{
		question:
			"Who is the most expensive signing in Premier League history?",
		answer: "Paul Pogba",
		options: [
			"Cristiano Ronaldo",
			"Erling Haaland",
			"Paul Pogba",
			"Romelu Lukaku",
		],
	},
	{
		question:
			"Which club has the most goals in a single Premier League season?",
		answer: "Manchester City",
		options: ["Liverpool", "Arsenal", "Chelsea", "Manchester City"],
	},
	{
		question: "Which Manager has the most league titles?",
		answer: "Alex Fergusen",
		options: [
			"Pep Guadiola",
			"Rafeal Benitez",
			"Alex Fergusen",
			"Jose Mourinho",
		],
	},

	{
		question: "Which English team has won the most UEFA Champions League?",
		answer: "Liverpool",
		options: [
			"Manchester United",
			"Liverpool",
			"Nothingham Forest",
			"Chelsea",
		],
	},
	{
		question: "Which of these English teams has Lukaku not played for?",
		answer: "WestHam",
		options: ["WestBrom", "Everton", "WestHam", "Chelsea"],
	},
];

let level2Questions = [
	{
		question: "Which club has the most Premier League clean sheets?",
		answer: "Chelsea",
		options: ["Arsenal", "Manchester City", "Chelsea", "Liverpool"],
	},
	{
		question:
			"Which club has won the Premier League title with the most games to spare?",
		answer: "Manchester City",
		options: [
			"Manchester City",
			"Manchester United",
			"Chelsea",
			"Liverpool",
		],
	},
	{
		question:
			"Who is the all-time leading goal scorer in the Premier League?",
		answer: "Alan Shearer",
		options: [
			"Alan Shearer",
			"Harry Kane",
			"Wayne Rooney",
			"Mohammed Salah",
		],
	},
	{
		question:
			"Which team holds the record for the most points in a single Premier League season?",
		answer: "Manchester City",
		options: [
			"Manchester City",
			"Manchester United",
			"Chelsea",
			"Liverpool",
		],
	},
	{
		question:
			"Who holds the record for the most goals in a single Premier League season?",
		answer: "Mohamed Salah",
		options: [
			"Mohamed Salah",
			"Thiery Henry",
			"Cristiano Ronaldo",
			"Erling Haaland",
		],
	},
	{
		question:
			"Which club has won the Premier League title with the lowest number of points?",
		answer: "Manchester United",
		options: [
			"Manchester City",
			"Liverpool",
			"Arsenal",
			"Manchester United",
		],
	},
];

let level3Questions = [
	{
		question:
			"Who is the only player to have won the Premier League with two different clubs in consecutive seasons?",
		answer: "N'Golo Kanté",
		options: [
			"N'Golo Kanté",
			"Alexis Sanchez",
			"Frank Lampard",
			"Romelu Lukaku",
		],
	},
	{
		question:
			"Who holds the record for the fastest Premier League hat-trick?",
		answer: "Sadio Mané",
		options: ["Sadio Mane", "Mohammed Salah", "Harry Kane", "Eden Hazard"],
	},
	{
		question:
			"Which team won the inaugural Premier League season in 1992-1993?",
		answer: "Manchester United",
		options: [
			"Newcastle United",
			"Liverpool",
			"Arsenal",
			"Manchester United",
		],
	},
	{
		question:
			"Who is the youngest player to reach 100 Premier League goals?",
		answer: "Harry Kane",
		options: ["Harry Kane", "Bukayo Saka", "Marcus Rashford", "Ivan Toney"],
	},
	{
		question: "Which team has won the most FA Cup titles?",
		answer: "Arsenal",
		options: ["Arsenal", "Manchester United", "Liverpool", "Chelsea"],
	},
	{
		question:
			"Which club has won the most consecutive Premier League games?",
		answer: "Manchester City",
		options: [
			"Manchester City",
			"Chelsea",
			"Manchester United",
			"Leicester United",
		],
	},
];

let level4Questions = [
	{
		question:
			"Who holds the record for the most Premier League assists in a single season?",
		answer: "Thierry Henry",
		options: [
			"Mezut Ozil",
			"Thierry Henry",
			"Ryan Giggs",
			"Kelvin DeBrynue",
		],
	},
	{
		question:
			"Who is the only player to have scored a hat-trick in the Manchester derby?",
		answer: "Sergio Aguero",
		options: [
			"Cristiano Ronaldo",
			"Edin Dzeko",
			"Javier Hernandez",
			"Sergio Aguero",
		],
	},
	{
		question:
			"Who is the youngest player to score a Premier League hat-trick?",
		answer: "James Vaughan",
		options: [
			"Cristiano Ronaldo",
			"Marcus Rashford",
			"James Vaughan",
			"Micheal Owen",
		],
	},
	{
		question:
			"Who is the only player to have scored five goals in a single Premier League game?",
		answer: "Andrew Cole",
		options: [
			"Andrew Cole",
			"Alan Shearer",
			"Erling Haaland",
			"Micheal Owen",
		],
	},
	{
		question: "Which team has won the most consecutive FA Cup titles?",
		answer: "Blackburn Rovers",
		options: [
			"Blackburn Rovers",
			"Arsenal",
			"Manchester United",
			"Newcastle United",
		],
	},
	{
		question:
			"Which team has the most top-four finishes in Premier League history?",
		answer: "Manchester United",
		options: ["Manchester City", "Tottenham", "Chelsea", "Arsenal"],
	},
];

let level5Questions = [
	{
		question: "Who is the youngest captain in Premier League history?",
		answer: "Phil Jagielka",
		options: [
			"Phil Jagielka",
			"John Stones",
			"Martin Odegaard",
			"Bruno Fernandez",
		],
	},
	{
		question: "Who is the oldest goal scorer in the Premier League?",
		answer: "Teddy Sheringham",
		options: [
			"Micheal Ballack",
			"Teddy Sheringham",
			"John Terry",
			"Zlatan Ibrahimovic",
		],
	},
	{
		question:
			"Which player has won the most Premier League Player of the Month awards?",
		answer: "Harry Kane",
		options: [
			"Marcus Rashford",
			"Harry Kane",
			"Didier Drogba",
			"Thiery Henry",
		],
	},
	{
		question:
			"Who is the first goalkeeper to have scored a goal in the Premier League?",
		answer: "Tim Howard",
		options: [
			"Edwin Van der ser",
			"Tim Howard",
			"Jordon Pickford",
			"Joe Hart",
		],
	},
	{
		question:
			"Who is the only player to have scored a hat-trick of penalties in a Premier League game?",
		answer: "Yakubu",
		options: ["Ronaldo", "Yakubu", "Kane", "Salah"],
	},
	{
		question:
			"Who is the oldest outfield player to appear in a Premier League match?",
		answer: "John Burridge",
		options: [
			"Zlatan Ibrahimovic",
			"John Burridge",
			"Paul Scholes",
			"Ryan Giggs",
		],
	},
];
